Fiona Papiez

Professional Carer

Contact

74 Hebron Road Stokesley North Yorkshire TS9 5DF

Fiona.papiez@live.com

Tel:(01642) 984542 Mob:07910119707

Key Skills

- 2+ years in care work
- NVQII Qualified (Adult Health and Social Care)
- Fast,accurate typist (50wpm+)
- Experienced user of Microsoft Office packages
- Ability to maintain confidentiality
- Excellent spelling and grammar
- Ability to work to a deadline/ under pressure

Full U.K. Driving licence

References available on request

Personal Statement

I began working as a carer in May 2014. I was completely new to this type of work but I found it very fulfilling. Since becoming a care worker I have learned much about the importance of dignity and compassion when helping vulnerable people. I thoroughly enjoy my job and the opportunity it gives me to be part of a close knit group working to benefit the local community. In February 2015 I was appointed to the position of Medication Senior for the Stokesley area, reflecting my increasing experience and confidence in my role. I have acted as the out of hours contact at Comfort Call for the North Yorkshire area. In this role I was responsible for managing employee schedules to ensure out of hours coverage and deal with unforeseen circumstances.

In the past I have held a variety of administration/secretarial roles from my recent work at Tata Global Beverages and Univar, to my 13 years at Teesside University and my first job at the Probation Service. The skills I developed range from data-entry, scanning, general correspondence and transcription; to administrative duties such as arranging meetings, travel and conferences, diary management, minute-production, maintenance of staff records and ordering of stationery. In all of these positions I have been required to work with confidential information in both electronic and paper formats. I have excellent verbal and written communication skills, am a fast and accurate typist and have experience with the Microsoft Office suite.

Employment

05/2014 - present Carer

Comfort Call Ltd

My clients range from those with profound disabilities through illness, such as MS, to those who simply need the reassurance of a daily call. In February 2015 I was made Medication Senior for the Stokesley area. In July 2016 I was made a senior carer for North Yorkshire.

10/2013 - 04/2014 **Data-Entry/Q.A. Assistant**

Tata Global Beverages, Eaglescliffe

Selecting samples from production lines, preparing tissue samples, conducting various quality tests, recording data in Microsoft Excel.

12/2012 - 10/2013 Production operative / Packer

Quorn Foods, Stokesley

Working as part of a team on the Production Line. Duties include packing, palletising, 'spotting', cleaning, some work in 'high-care' production areas.

11/2012 - 12/2012 Temporary Administrative Assistant

Univar Europe, Middlesbrough

General administrative/clerical duties including typing, filing, scanning/photocopying/faxing, emailing, answering the telephone, dataentry (Microsoft Office, Excel, Outlook, Word). The company were in the process of migrating to new office management software and I was involved in the scanning, uploading and data-entry of mass documents into SAP.

1996-2004 Personal Assistant to my ex-husband

Freelance IT consultancy

Typing, filing, answering the telephone, making travel arrangements, preparing invoices etc.

07/1980 - 04/1991 **Deparmental Assistant**

Teesside University; Computer Centre

Provision of clerical and secretarial support to senior staff, production/typing of minutes and correspondence (from dictation or audio), technical documents, PhD theses etc. Conference organisation, reception duties including setting-up student and staff accounts on the computer systems. Ordering stationery, recording holidays and sickness, organising travel and accommodation for Centre staff.

11/1978 - 07-1980 **Shorthand/Typist**

Teesside University; Central Administration

As a member of the Typing Pool, providing a typing service to Administrative and other university staff. This job also involved being seconded to academic departments to provide secretarial support.

08/1978 - 11/1978 **Shorthand/Typist/Clerk**

Cleveland Probation Service; Headquarters

Providing secretarial support to the Administrative Officer.

Education

2016 Working towards NVQIII Health & Social Care (Adult)

Lifetime Learning

2015 NVQ II Health & Social Care (Adult)

Lifetime Learning

09/2012 - 10/2012 Edexcel BTEC Level 2 Certificate in Supporting Employability and Personal Effectiveness.

1996-1999 Diploma in Music

The Open University

Modules Studied: A102 Arts Foundation Course, A214 Understanding Music, AA302 From Composition to Performance.

1977-1978 LCCI Secretarial Studies Certificate

Kirby College of Further Education

Components included Typing, Shorthand, Audio-Typing, Office Practice, English, Business Studies; RSA Typing II, RSA English; Pitman Shorthand, various speeds up to 120wpm. Pitman Typing/Audio Typing

1975-1977 **GCE O-Levels**

Stokesley School

English Language C, English Literature C, History C, CSE French 2, German 2, Art & Design, Typing.

Voluntary Work

2004 Shop Assistant

Help the Aged, Stokesley

01/1985 - 07/1986 **Sub-Warden** Teesside University (Polytechnic); Middleton-St-George Halls of Residence This residential post involved assisting students with any problems regarding their accommodation, arranging for repairs and maintenance with the senior warden, inspecting rooms and booking in/out students at the start and end of term, carrying out fire-drills.